{
  "java_quiz": [
      {
          "id": "java_quiz_question1",
          "quizType": "Java Quiz",
          "questionType": "true_false",
          "questionText": "Java is a programming language that is object oriented.",
          "correctAnswer": "True",
          "options": ["True", "False"],
          "explanation": "Java is a general-purpose, class-based, and object-oriented programming language."
      },
      {
          "id": "java_quiz_question2",
          "quizType": "Java Quiz",
          "questionType": "multiple_choice",
          "questionText": "Which statement would you use to print the string \"stripey\" in Java?",
          "correctAnswer": "System.out.println(\"stripey\")",
          "options":["console.log(\"stripey\")", "Console.WriteLine(\"stripey\")", "System.out.println(\"stripey\")", "print('stripey')"],
          "explanation": "If one wishes to print using java, you use the iconic System.out.println() method "
      },
      {
        "id": "java_quiz_question3",
        "quizType": "Java Quiz",
        "questionType": "text_input_multiple",
        "questionText": "There are three types of loops you can use in Java. One is a for loop. What are the names of the other two kinds of loops one can encounter?",
        "correctAnswer": ["do-while", "while"],
        "answerFieldOneId": "first_answer",
        "answerFieldTwoId": "second_answer",
        "explanation": "The other two kinds of loops are the do-while and the while loops.(tried to trick u with 2 similar)"
    },
      
      {
          "id": "java_quiz_question4",
          "quizType": "Java Quiz",
          "questionType": "text_input_one",
          "questionText": "What Java statement do you need to find the 7?",
          "correctAnswer": "Math.sqrt(7)",
          "answerFieldId": "answer_to_question",
          "explanation": "To find the square root of any numberin Java, one way is to use the Math.sqrt() method."
      }, 
      
      {
        "id": "java_quiz_question5",
        "quizType": "Java Quiz",
        "questionType": "image_selection",
        "questionText": "Which code block will print the phrase \"aaa\"? Click the image showing the correct code block below.",
        "correctAnswer": "img_2",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": "img_1",
                "source": ""
            }, 
            {
                "id": "img_2",
                "source": ""
            }
        ],
        "explanation": "In the 2nd image, the loop iterates three times (i = 0, i = 1, i = 2). Once i = 3, the loop stops. In the first image, the loop continues until i > 3, so it executes four times (i = 0, i = 1, i = 2, i = 3)."
    },
    {
      "id": "java_quiz_question6",
      "quizType": "Java Quiz",
      "questionType": "text_input_multiple",
      "questionText": "what are 2 access modifiers used in Java(dont worry there are 4 you can think of).",
      "correctAnswer": ["public", "private", "protected", "default"],
      "answerFieldOneId": "first_answer",
      "answerFieldTwoId": "second_answer",
      "explanation": "The four access modifiers in Java are public, private, protected, and default."
    },
    {
        "id": "java_quiz_question7",
        "quizType": "Java Quiz",
        "questionType": "true_false",
        "questionText": " An Overridden method is a type of method with the same name that have different parameters.",
        "correctAnswer": "False",
        "options": ["True", "False"],
        "explanation": "A method that has the same name but different parameters are called overloaded methods. An Overridden method are actually inherited from a superclass with different functionality than in the superclass it is in."
    },
    {
        "id": "java_quiz_question8",
        "quizType": "Java Quiz",
        "questionType": "text_input_one",
        "questionText": "what are the ony possible values for booleans .",
            "correctAnswer": "true or false",
            "answerFieldId": "answer_to_question",
            "explanation": " Booleans are fundamental for making decisions in programming through conditional statements and loops. They only are true or false.;"
        },
        {
            "id": "java_quiz_question9",
            "quizType": "Java Quiz",
            "questionType": "text_input_multiple",
            "questionText": "What are the two most common types used in Java coding to store numbers?",
            "correctAnswer": ["double", "int"],
            "answerFieldOneId": "first_answer",
            "answerFieldTwoId": "second_answer",
            "explanation": "Java has many ways for storing numbers. However, the most common types used by most java coders are int and double."
        },
        {
            "id": "java_quiz_question10",
            "quizType": "Java Quiz",
            "questionType": "image_selection",
            "questionText": "Which of the following code snippets correctly initializes an array of integers in Java?",
            "correctAnswer": "img_2",
            "options": [
                {
                    "id": "img_1",
                    "source": ""
                  }, 
                {
                    "id": "img_2",
                    "source": ""
                }
            ],
            "explanation": " In Java, to initialize an array of integers, the correct syntax is to use square brackets [] after the data type. Image 1 has the brackets in the wrong place so it wouldn't run properly."
        },
        
      {
        "id": "java_quiz_question11",
        "quizType":"Java Quiz",
        "questionType":"multiple_choice",
        "questionText": "What would be the correct syntax for creating an object of the sportball class named BowlingBall?",
        "correctAnswer": "sportball bowlingball = new sportball();",
        "options": ["new sportball(BowlingBall);", "BowlingBall = Object.create(sportball);", "sportball.BowlingBall);", "sportball BowlingBall = new sportball();"],
        "explanation": "the correct syntax is: ClassName name = new ClassName();. since the name of the object is \"BowlingBall\" and the name of the class is \"sportball\" the correct syntax is Ball basketball = new Ball();"
    }
  ]
}
      